bridalmusings.com 2017-06-06

# Policies - Bridal Musings

## Editorial Policy

Bridal Musings features a wide range of inspiring and helpful wedding related content.

In addition to our regular content, such as real weddings, styled shoots and advice posts, we also feature sponsored content and affiliate links on Bridal Musings. This is how we are able to pay the BM team for their talent, hard work and time, and how we cover business costs such as website and image hosting, professional storage solutions, photo editing software, social media scheduling tools etc.

We always write from the heart and only ever promote brands, products and services that we genuinely love and think our readers will love and/or appreciate too.

## Disclosure

In the interests of full transparency, sponsored posts will always be clearly disclosed with the words ‘Sponsored By…’, ‘Sponsored Post’, ‘Partnered Post’ or ‘written in partnership with…’ in the post title or at the top of the post and sponsored social shares will be marked with #Ad. The use of affiliate links will be also disclosed at the bottom of each post or page on Bridal Musings where they are present.

## Affiliate Links

We sometimes use affiliate links on the site and our social channels. This simply means that if you click on a link we’ve shared and make a purchase from an affiliate site, Bridal Musings will receive a very small percentage of the sale. It’s a little reward for recommending the product that doesn’t affect you in any way (but helps us out a lot). If you don’t purchase anything, or if you purchase something and return it, we don’t receive any compensation.

Please note the ‘Shop’ section of Bridal Musings (coming soon!) and ‘Shop The Look’ widgets feature affiliate links. But, as with everything you see on Bridal Musings, a lot of love and care goes into curating our shop and we only ever feature products we love and think you will too.

All of the content on Bridal Musings is published with the best available information we have at the time of publication. However, product offerings, websites, and businesses change, so we cannot guarantee that all archived links and content remain accurate as of the time of reading.

## Privacy Policy

We value your privacy. This policy document outlines how personal information is received, collected, and used.

## What Information Do We Collect?

We collect your name and email address if you choose to subscribe to our newsletter, and we may also collect other information from you if you choose to take part in reader surveys or enter reader giveaways. This information is never shared with 3rd parties, unless required by law.

## Third Party Ad Servers And Networks

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioural advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit  [www.networkadvertising.org.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Bridal Musings. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Bridal Musings and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy here: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

## Links To Other Websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.

## Consent

By accessing Bridal Musings and providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of this information in accordance with this policy.

Please note Bridal Musings may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. This policy is effective from 19th July 2016.
